"use strict";(self.webpackChunk_3dls=self.webpackChunk_3dls||[]).push([[184],{289:function(t,s,e){e.r(s),s.default=[{id:"hotspot-1",title:1,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"esophagus",dataSurface:"5 0 205 206 203 0.399 0.522 0.079",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-2",title:2,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"liver",dataSurface:"1 0 62 64 65 0.046 0.639 0.314",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-3",title:3,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"stomach",dataSurface:"5 0 11 10 9 0.682 0.249 0.069",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-4",title:4,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"gallbladder",dataSurface:"7 0 134 131 132 0.690 0.174 0.135",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-5",title:5,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"ascending colon",dataSurface:"0 0 1052 1117 1106 0.105 0.327 0.569",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-6",title:6,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"transverse colon",dataSurface:"0 0 3855 3790 3789 0.528 0.223 0.249",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-7",title:7,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"descending colon",dataSurface:"0 0 7114 7116 7101 0.284 0.215 0.502",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-8",title:8,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"sigmoid colon",dataSurface:"0 0 9309 9245 9244 0.743 0.003 0.254",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-9",title:9,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"rectum",dataSurface:"0 0 10395 10383 557 0.670 0.272 0.058",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-10",title:10,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"anus",dataSurface:"0 0 10490 10508 10506 0.864 0.003 0.133",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-11",title:11,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"small intestine",dataSurface:"4 0 2167 2168 2169 0.335 0.308 0.356",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-12",title:12,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"pharynx",dataSurface:"2 0 270 271 272 0.625 0.304 0.072",userAnswer:""},{id:"hotspot-13",title:13,question:"\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05d3\u05d4 \u05d6\u05d5 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0:",options:[],answer:"larynx",dataSurface:"2 0 231 228 229 0.610 0.253 0.137",userAnswer:""}]}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=184.073c8c14.chunk.js.map